Name Bodey Royce Baker
Date of Birth 5th October 1984
Citizenship Australian

 Email
 bodey.baker@gmail.com

 Phone
 +82-10-2186-1005

 Location
 Seoul, South Korea

#### Summary

I am a native English speaker from Australia living in Korea and hoping to get some more experience teaching for a few years.

Previously I've worked teaching English in primary schools and junior high schools both following a curriculum and planning my own lessons. I've also tutored and demonstrated for engineering and programming units at the University of Western Australia as well as attending their "Seminars, Tutorials and Laboratories" teaching course. During my time working and studying at this university I published three academic papers and presented two at conferences. One of these was during the honours research year of my Computer Science degree where I topped the unit "Scientific Communication", a unit concentrating on academic writing.

I really enjoy teaching and now I'd like to expand the teaching skills and experience I currently have.



#### Experience

#### **Avionics Software Engineer**

- Worked in a professional setting programming and designing software for UAVs.
- Wrote internal documentation and manuals.

July 2010 - July 2012 Cyber Technology Australia

#### July 2009 - November 2009 University of Western Australia

#### Tutor

- Tutored the units:
  - Modelling and Computing Analysis for Engineers
  - Java
- Required ability to explain difficult concepts to students who were struggling.
- Duties: teaching, lab demonstrating and marking.

#### Undergraduate Engineer

 Presented reports on the analysis of accelerometer data to ensure vehicles met vibration requirements. May 2009 - June 2010 JRB Engineering Australia

#### **Assistant English Teacher**

- Taught English to primary and junior high school students.
- $\bullet$  Duties: planning lessons; teaching; communicating with students.
- Skills: teaching; public speaking; motivating others; integrating into new cultures.

## $\begin{array}{c} \textbf{May 2008 - February 2009} \\ \textbf{W5 Staff Services} \\ \textbf{Japan} \end{array}$

#### Undergraduate Engineer

• Wrote software to visualise log files so that others could easily identify problems.

January 2008 - March 2008 JRB Engineering Australia

#### Research Assistant

• Tested a method to explore the structure of a rock sample from 3D data and visualise the output using a 3D projector.

August 2007 - January 2008 iVEC at the ARRC Australia

#### July 2007 - November 2007 University of Western Australia

- Tutored the units:
  - Modelling and Computing Analysis for Engineers
  - Mechatronics Systems
  - Java

#### Research Assistant

December 2006 - December 2007 Centre for Exploration Targeting University of Western Australia

- Studied how roughness changes with direction across rock surfaces.
- Finished with a talk and poster explaining the results to the public
- Published a paper with an academic journal

#### Education

#### Bachelor of Engineering (Mechatronics)

2011: The University of Western Australia

The final year project took an expensive damage detection system and modified it to use cheaper and smaller electronics. This required design, planning, mathematical analysis of sensor readings, and finally a public talk explaining the project.

#### **Bachelor of Computer Science**

2006: The University of Western Australia

The final year project was "Strategy specification for teamwork in robot soccer". This project ended with a conference paper being presented in front of other researchers and students. Also, because the project used robot dogs, we often did demonstration shows entertaining children and their parents.

#### Scholarships and Prizes

**2007:** Top of the Computer Science honours unit "Scientific Communication" **2001:** Institute of Engineers award for attaining a TEE score above 75% in:

Chemistry, Physics, Calculus and Applicable Mathematics.

2000: Olympic Torch Escort Runner

#### Professional affiliations

2007-2008: Webmaster of Ancestrais Capoeira

**2007:** President of the UWA Association of Mechatronics Engineers **2006:** Social Engineer of the UWA Association of Mechatronics Engineers

2006: Vice-President of the UWA Computer Science Students' Club

2005: Ordinary Committee Member in the UWA Computer Science Students' Club

#### Interests

Soccer, Rock Climbing, Acrobatics, Capoeira, Machine Learning, Languages, Snow Boarding, Travelling, Cultures.



## The University of Western Australia

In the name of the Senate and by authority of the same

be it known that

# Bodey Royce Baker

having fulfilled all the requirements was admitted to the degree of

# Bachelor of Engineering (Mechatronics Engineering)

and to all the privileges attached to the same on the date stated hereunder



Vice-Chancellor

Registrar

Date: 20 September 2011



## The University of Western Australia

In the name of the Senate and by authority of the same

be it known that

# Bodey Royce Baker

having fulfilled all the requirements was admitted to the degree of

# Bachelor of Computer Science

with Second Class Honours
(Division A)

and to all the privileges attached to the same on the date stated hereunder



Vice-Chancellor

Registrar

Date: 20 September 2011

10 January 2007

Mr Bodey R. Baker 42 Williams Road NEDLANDS WA 6009 School of Computer Science and Software Engineering

The University of Western Australia 35 Stirling Highway, Crawley WA 6009

Phone + 61 8 6488 2716 Fax + 61 8 6488 1089 Email head@csse.uwa.edu.au

MBDP: M002

CRICOS Provider Code: 00126G

Dear Mr Baker

#### HIGHEST MARK - CITS7200 SCIENTIFIC COMMUNICATION

On behalf of the staff of the School of Computer Science & Software Engineering, but particularly Dr Lyndon While, I would like to congratulate you on achieving the highest mark in the above unit for 2006.

It is a pleasure for all academics to teach students who achieve such good grades in their subjects and who thus contribute to the intellectual life of the School. I wish you all the best in your future studies.

Yours sincerely

Dr Nick Spadaccini

Nickfpadaccini

Head of School

cc Dr Lyndon While - Unit Coordinator